Profile

During the last five years as a designer, I've been working with companies from various industries. My focus is to creating user-centric and human experiences solutions. Thanks to my background interests in psychology and development, I connect these knowledge with real business goals, and my ambition is to provide experiences of the user's needs.

Experience

UX UI Designer

2020 - 2022

Suera.io

Researched and identified problems in complex leading niche and start-up products. Designed and validated workflows experience solutions and close collaborated with multiple dev roles to drive alignments of the user and business needs.

UX UI Designer

2019 - 2020

The House

Define and deep understanding of user-centred problems, and strong analytical studies for a wide range of platforms including desktop apps, responsive web, web applications, native applications, and more.

Design Instructor

2020 - 3 months

IT Step

Taught the design students basic skills, approaches, and tools to effectively and compellingly communicate their ideas. Designed the course structure and interaction in learning curve.

Web Designer

2018 - 2019

Spendid

Design in eCommerce CMS solutions and flex applications for medium-sized businesses. Conduct design process and communication with clients.

Freelancer (one man army designer)

2017 - 2018

Upwork

Communication with clients and preparation of proposals to international clients from small and medium businesses. Preparation and implementation of pre-assigned tasks related to the execution of landing pages and brand identity.

Find more about me:

Linkedin Behance
Kristiyan Monchev monchevdesign

Dribbble monchev-design

Education

Google UX Design

Jan 2022

Complete fully 7 course's of google academic program.

Telerik Academy

June 2021

Upskill UX/UI Program

Interaction Design Foundation (IXDF)

Sep 2021

Brain Science in Interface Design

May 2021

Human-Computer Interaction

Apr 2021

Design Thinking

Software Academy

Jule 2020

Web Development

Design Academy

Jule 2019

Brand Identity & Graphic design

Skills

Design

Adobe CC, Figma, Sketch, Principe, Invision, Whimsical, Stark, Axure, Cinema 4D, Marvel, Flowchart, Justinmind, Abstract, Framer, UXpin, Miro, Mural, Maze.

Collaborate with dev from:

Angular, React, Flutter, Ionic, React Native, Xamarine.